The Legend Is Born
Almighty Thor is a adventure, fantasy, tv movie
film directed by Christopher Ray.
Loki destroys the fortress of Valhalla and steals the Hammer of Invincibility,
only the young hero Thor can protect Earth from Armageddon.
Thor, played by Cody Deal.
Jarnsaxa, played by Patricia Velásquez.
Loki, played by Richard Grieco.
Odin, played by Kevin Nash.
Baldir, played by Jess Allen.
Himdall, played by Chris Ivan Cevic.
Almighty Thor is a 2011 American superhero television
film directed by Christopher Olen Ray.
The film, a mockbuster coinciding with the release of the Marvel
Studios film Thor, was produced by The Asylum for $200,000.
It premiered on the Syfy cable network on May 7, 2011 and was
released on DVD on May 10, 2011 in the United States.
The film was met with a largely negative response from critics.
Loosely inspired by Norse mythology, the film follows the young warrior
Thor (Cody Deal) in his battle against Loki (Richard Grieco).
In 2022, The Asylum released a second Thor film titled Thor: God of Thunder.
The film explores themes of saving the world, mythology,
armageddon, norse mythology, norse god.